♪ It seems today
that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies
and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those
good old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪♪
Hey, Meg. What are you up to?
Not much. Just finished
an angel food cake.
Might go out to the trash, see
if there's any possums to kiss.
I was just out there.
Oh, come on,
it's your senior year.
Somebody must be having a party
or something.
Well, there's one.
But... I wasn't invited.
Well, so what? Go crash it.
Nah. Not my style.
And what do you care?
Do you want the TV or something?
What? No, no. I want...
I want to see you have fun.
Come on, you should go,
you know? Let loose a little.
You know what? You're right.
Maybe I will give it a shot.
Yeah. How awkward could it be?
Can't be worse
than waving at someone
who doesn't wave back at you.
- No, not you.
- Oh. Sorry.
In fact, everyone but you.
Hi, everyone but him!
Hi!
Lou, I like you a lot, but
I-I think that's the last tape
of you having sex with
your girlfriend I want to see.
Suit yourself.
All right, I got to get over
to my mom's wake.
Oh, right, yeah. Crap.
Ugh. Sorry again.
- Oof. Cancer.
- Car accident.
No, I know, I just, I'm...
saying it feels like
everyone's getting cancer.
You know, Bowie.
Time to get creepay...
Huh. Kid family.
What a scumbag.
Aw...
Because I'm working all day!
Oh, yeah? Well, here's what
I think of your stupid work!
Don't you do that!
Fiona, don't you...
Is that Principal Shepherd?
Wow, that looks like
a rocky relationship.
"Rocky relationship."
Ha-ha!
Oh, come on, Brian.
Don't comment or like it.
It's a hard lesson,
but one he has to learn.
♪♪ Electronic dance music playing...
♪♪
♪♪ Electronic dance music resumes...
All right, ladies,
time to mingle.
Hey. You guys
talking Big Bang over here?
Big Bang Theory?
No? Any Bangers over here?
No?
Well, I've tried everything.
We just don't have anything
in common with these guys.
Maybe... we don't need
anything in common with them.
Meg, come on, don't go crazy.
Damn, that's hot!
That was just lucky.
Oh, yeah?
Wow! Meg's so good
at casually tossing bottles
over her shoulder
so they land upright!
And that's very popular
right now,
because we've
run out of things on Earth.
Meg, that was amazing!
What can I say?
I'm full of surprises.
Like the end
of The Usual Suspects.
♪♪
He was gay the whole time!
♪ Boughs of holly ♪
♪ Rockin' around... ♪
Okay, they're obviously home.
You'd have to be dumb
to try to rob that place.
Oh, yes!
I hate the guy, but he's good.
Oh, my God.
What the... what the hell
is going on over there?
Did he...
- Hello. -
- Hey, Stewie, it's me.
You got a second?
Brian? Hang on.
Hey, keep it down,
you screwballs.
Here, let me just go
somewhere a little quieter.
Oh, yeah, right. I'm the screwball.
You and friends
say "screwball" a lot.
That's what happens when
you run with a screwy crowd.
What's up with you?
Stewie, I think...
I think Principal Shepherd
killed his wife.
What? What are you
talking about?
I think I saw him
getting rid of her body.
And carrying a bag
with something heavy in it.
And... and there was red liquid
dripping from it.
Okay, I've got to see this
for myself.
Don't do anything.
I'm coming over.
Hey, listen,
you-you don't think...
you don't think you
could snag a couple of rolls
of toilet paper, could you?
- Stewie?
- I'm here. I just wanted you
to have to sit with those words
for a minute.
Kids, dinner's ready!
"Dinner's ready."
Shut up.
Little of the old schnappster
ought to get me right.
'Ey... Chrissay!
Well, that's
delightfully informal, Meg.
How the heck are ya?
♪♪
So, what are you kids
doing in school?
I got in trouble for saying
something "insensitive"
to trans kids.
- What'd you say?
- Well, a few them started
this a cappella group,
and they're all kind of chubby.
So I said, "You guys should
call yourselves the Trans Fats."
Meg, you'll sit
next to me this evening.
- But, Dad...
- I'm sorry, Chris. You've fallen out of favor.
Perhaps forever.
Oh, Stewie,
thank God you're here.
There's a seagull
in your hallway.
Listen, what are we gonna do
about this
Principal Shepherd thing?
Look, all you know is that
the guy was carrying a wet bag.
It doesn't mean
he killed his wife.
You're building this whole theory...
What is that noise?
It's a news alert.
"Fiona Shepherd, wife of James
Woods High School principal
John Shepherd,
has been reported missing."
Oh, my God, maybe he did do it.
You know, there are
some bad people in this world.
Hey, you don't got
to tell me that.
I learned that in Fight Club.
All right, Stewie, what's
the first rule of Fight Club?
G-string underwear.
No. It's "don't talk
about Fight Club."
Oh. Well, I really blew it.
♪♪
Hey-o! What's up in this piece?
You're getting home late.
Yeah. We were hanging out
in the woods, and...
this one girl pushed
another girl over
while she was peeing.
They fought,
and then the cops came.
Meg, this is important.
Did she fall in the pee?
I can smell your breath.
You've been drinking,
haven't you?
No! Geez, Mom, get off my back.
Peter, I think
she's doing booze.
What should we do?
Lois, she's just being
a teenager.
We don't know she's, like, for
sure, definitely been drinking.
I found this in her room.
My little girl's a drunk!
Oh, my God,
where did we go wrong?
♪♪
Meg, we need to talk.
What, Mom? But I know
what you're gonna say,
and I know how
you're gonna say it.
- Oh, really?
- Yep.
I don't want you drinkin'
or your life's
gonna go down the crappah.
That's not bad.
I-I mean,
I sound nothing like that,
but it's a fun character. Heh.
But this is serious.
Alcoholism runs in our family.
Hey, I'm just glad
something runs in this family.
I don't mean to...
I-I don't mean to laugh, okay?
But that was funny.
Mom, I'm just having fun.
I'm finally known as something
other than "the chubby girl
who put the lunch lady
in a headlock."
And besides, Dad's the one
who pushed me
into going to that party.
Oh, he did, did he?
Son of a bitch.
What was that?
I don't know. Someone
must've messed something up.
Listen, you need to talk to Meg
about her drinking.
What? Why me?
Because you're the one
who told her
to start going
to these parties.
Okay, fine.
I guess it's just something
I got to deal with.
Like the flush
of a high-powered toilet.
♪♪
So, you plan on going back
at that banana, huh?
So the bastard killed his wife,
and then reported her missing.
I-I got to...
I got to call the cops.
- Quahog Police.
- Joe, Joe, it's Brian.
Listen, I have
to tell you something.
I-I'm pretty sure
Principal Shepherd
killed his wife.
That's a serious accusation.
Do you have any proof?
I have something better
than proof:
rank suspicion born out
of boredom and loneliness.
Sorry, that's just not enough
for us to go on.
You must be pretty tired
from thinking about all this.
- You ever get bags under your eyes?
- What?
I've been using this eye cream,
it's done wonders for me.
It's made by a company
called Rodan and Fields.
Have you heard of them, Brian?
Yeah, I-I think, uh...
Oh, they make terrific stuff.
In fact, I was such a fan,
I became a sales consultant
for the company.
Listen, Joe, I got to run.
I'm hosting a little
get-together tomorrow night,
If you want to stop by.
There's gonna be pizza
and soft drinks, then a man's
gonna talk about the whole line.
Can I go ahead
and confirm your attendance?
Well, that was no help.
What if I go over there
and try to find some evidence
- that he did it?
- All right, fine.
But you have to be careful.
Don't worry,
he won't have any idea.
I'll be more discreet
than a guy standing by himself
in the ocean.
Hey, are you peeing?
No.
Are you pooping?
I'm just trying
to enjoy the day.
Why don't you
go bother that guy?
Summer's blown by, huh?
♪♪
So, your mom says
you've been drinking.
Yeah, like, a little bit, but...
but it's nothing
you have to worry about.
Look, I-I was young,
too, you know.
I-I remember going to parties,
walking up with a six pack.
You're so excited to get there,
you start jogging a little.
Your friends are all there,
and they're so happy to see you,
they're practically cheering
your name.
And then "Mony Mony" comes on
at just the right time.
And everyone's dancing,
and-and Laura Hallston's jugs
are just slamming into you.
You don't have a care
in the world,
and if all of it came to an end
right then and there, so be it.
Well, you're my daughter,
and I don't want
any of that for you.
Hey, you want to see where I was
sitting when you were born?
Yeah, I still think
about Laura a lot.
You were already drinking
tonight, weren't you?
A little.
Well, I can't talk
to a drunk person if I'm sober.
Hey, Jerome,
can I get a beer, please?
But now I'm starting
to sober up,
so I'm gonna need one
to keep an even playing field.
All right,
but it stays between us.
And what if they card you?
Don't worry. I got it covered.
Wow. That's really good.
Right?! Jerome, make it two!
♪ My girl wants
to party all the time ♪
♪ Party all the time,
party all the time ♪
♪ My girl wants
to party all the time ♪
♪ Party all the time ♪
♪ I buy you champagne and roses,
put diamonds on your finger ♪
♪ Diamonds on your finger ♪
♪ Party all the time ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh-ooh, ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh,
ooh-ooh, ooh-ooh, ooh-ooh ♪
♪ My girl wants
to party all the time ♪
♪ Party all the time ♪
♪ Yeah. ♪
All right, he's gone.
Now, if I give the word, you've
got to get out of there, okay?
Got it.
Oh, my God!
What? What is it?
He sleeps in a bunk bed!
Are you kidding me?!
Who is this guy?!
Wait a second. Is that...?
Bri, I'm gonna put you down
for a sec.
Stewie, no! Don't.
Stewie, get out of there!
Stewie! Stewie!
Got to get his attention.
Man, just short.
Oh, God.
Domino's.
Oh, good.
Medium pie, ten wings.
Is the blue cheese
dressing in there?
Thanks a lot. Have a good one.
Mmm.
He got out! Ha, ha!
Yes, Stewie!
Oh, crap.
Oh, my, that was close.
Stewie, he saw you! He saw you
leaving his apartment!
Oh. Well... so what?
He doesn't know
what we're doing.
Ah!
What? What is it?
Well, that's...
that's not good.
Dad? Dad, wake up!
- Huh? What happened?
- I don't know!
We must have stolen this boat
last night.
I-I have no idea
where the hell we are!
Oh, no, my cell phone's dead!
I got a little bit
of juice left,
so we can either
A, call someone,
maybe they answer,
maybe they can help,
or B, we can definitely
switch faces.
Look at you!
Look at me!
That's what this is!
Oh, we're gonna die.
Dad, what are we gonna do?
You think it's too early to tie
our shirts around our heads
to show we're going insane?
I mean it, Dad. This is serious.
I did pants instead.
Ugh! I don't feel so hot.
What is wrong with me?
Have you taken a break
since you started drinking?
Not until right now.
Do you feel like lying
on the couch, rubbing your eyes,
while listening
to Lou Reed's "Perfect Day"?
- Yes!
- Then I'll tell you what's wrong with you.
You got a hangover.
What can you do for a hangover?
Well, Meg,
so I don't have to think
about my throbbing headache,
I try to think of
something else, like a riddle.
Like, how would you describe
Chris O'Donnell?
Huh. He's not tall or short.
And he's not fat or thin.
Well, he's not handsome or ugly.
And he's not young or old.
He's not loud or quiet.
Uh, he's not memorable,
but-but I know who he is.
Ah!
Thanks, Dad!
I feel so much better.
But you know who doesn't?
Chris O'Donnell.
Bye, dildo.
Oh, no. Hard shoes on linoleum.
That's a principal!
Brian, a lot of people
live in this building,
and you can't tell it's
a principal just from a walk.
Excuse me? May I have
your attention, please?
Okay, that's probably
a principal.
Hey. How are you today?
What can I do for you?
What do you want from me?
Listen, it's...
it's-it's not what you think.
Then what is it?
Well... I'm, um...
I'm actually doing a documentary
about some
of the finest principals
in the country, and...
Ow! Continue.
"Finest principals
in the country" and...
Brian!
Stewie! Help me!
How did I get here?
Well, to answer that, you'd
have to go back a little while.
We're not doing that!
We found this in a Dumpster
behind Principal Shepherd's
building.
That's it.
That's-that's the bag!
I guarantee his wife's in there.
- Ha!
- What's the matter, Rook?
Too heavy for you?
I've actually been a cop
for years.
I have tummy cancer.
Oh. Weird way to say that.
What the hell? Bu-But I saw...
Yeah, well, what is all this?
Principal Shepherd,
I think you've got
some explaining to do.
Look, I tried to tell you,
I didn't kill my wife.
She just texted me today
that she's moved out
and she's banging my cousin,
Pat Sajak's accountant,
by the way.
It's a weird time to name drop.
And the food, well,
I've been stealing it
from the high school
to make ends meet.
My life's "kinda brute,"
as the kids say.
Sounds like
you've had a rough day.
No wonder you've got those bags
under your eyes.
Have you ever heard of a company
called Rodan and Fields?
Ugh. Are all hangovers this bad?
Yup, that's the deal
you make with the gods of fun.
Every 72 hours, you lose a day.
Dad, you're so sunburnt.
I can't move
because it hurts too bad.
Ugh. This is awful.
We don't even know
if anyone's looking for us.
Look, don't worry.
We're gonna be okay.
This is why you shouldn't drink.
Booze is nothing but trouble,
and you don't need it.
You got a good brain
in your head.
Thanks, Dad, and if this is what
drinking makes you feel like,
you don't have
to worry about it.
I am done with booze.
Aw, I'm glad to hear that.
And I'm sorry
I pushed it on you.
I just...
I just wanted to watch TV.
I don't want
to see you waste opportunities
'cause you were out partying.
That's what I did.
You just worry about being you.
Don't worry, Dad.
I'll never be anything like you.
That's my girl.
Dad, look!
Oh, my God.
Meg, we're saved!
Thank God you found us.
We're so glad
you picked us up...
- Chris O'Donnell?
- That's right.
And I hope
you like turbulence, dildos.
The actual Chris O'Donnell
is not a Coast Guard
helicopter pilot.
We assume
he's probably too short.
Oh, my God.
Brian, are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Annie, are you okay?
So, Annie, are you okay?
Are you okay, Annie?
What happened to her?
She was hit by, uh...
She was struck
by a smooth criminal.
That was fun, Mom.
We don't get to do a lot
of that kind of stuff together.
Listen, Brian,
we want you to come home again.
Oh, so the Twitter pariah
is finally welcome home?
No, but the school board
hero dog is.
It was all over the papers.
You saved the school $206
from all the food they recovered
from Principal Shepherd's
fridge.
So... you really want me
to come home?
They're still gonna serve
that food?
Of course we do.
Hey, where's everyone else?
Oh, my God.
Peter, what happened?
What happened? A fair question.
And to answer it,
we have to go back a ways.
- Stop doing that thing!
- Aw.
♪♪
Brian, I got to say, it's great
to have you home again, buddy.
Well, it's great to be here.
Living on my own was fun,
but I couldn't stop thinking
about all the stuff
I was missing
being away from you guys.
Did you ever finish
that banana, Brian?
And, Meg, I hope you learned
your lesson about drinking.
Yeah, I think I'd rather
live my life as a loser
than feel bad once in a while.
Well, I hope you know
that you're our loser.
Thanks, Mom.
If my life were better here,
would I stop searching for it...
up there?
Thank you for watching "Family Guy" on
www.FOX-fan.ru